I'm so mad!
Cheng An, just to get Kista into Gufeng Group,
he's stopping at nothing.
He's forcing me into a corner.
Calm down.
Don't be angry.
We'll figure out a solution.
I have to beat Kista.
Cheng An won't let me have it easy,
so I won't let him have it easy either.
I see it clearly now.
Rather than cooperating with him,
I'm better off relying on myself.
I'll let him know
that even without Cheng An,
I, Lin Wanmei, can still
stand firm in Gufeng Group.
Luoluo.
Come here.
Auntie Lin.
Here.
Taste my wine.
How is it?
The yeasty aroma from the sur lie aging
is faintly present at the finish.
The proportion of oak barrels used
is also precisely calculated.
Auntie Lin's winemaking skills
certainly live up to their reputation.
Sang Luo.
You seem to know a lot about red wine.
How did you manage that?
It's just that
Yi Kai
often takes me wine tasting worldwide.
After tasting so many,
I naturally picked up a few things.
I see.
How do you think I compare with Kista?
What's the difference between us?
Auntie Lin, today,
you didn't just invite me for wine, right?
What do you think?
I think
Auntie's early wines
are quite stunning in many ways.
They have a distinct style
and a strong personality.
As for Kista's wines, needless to say,
her selection of grape varieties
and her winemaking techniques
are strictly controlled.
Every wine is like a work of art.
So,
both of your wines
have their own merits.
Actually,
today, I
specially prepared a gift for you.
This is too valuable.
Auntie,
I can't accept this.
Don't be so polite with me.
I prepared it especially for you.
I hope you like it.
I like it.
Actually,
today,
there's something I need your help with.
I know you're close with Yi Kai.
I want you to help me get
info on Kista's latest red wine.
Ideally, if you could get me a few bottles
of Kista's unreleased wines.
You know what they say.
Know your enemy and know yourself,
and you will win every battle.
Well...
Luoluo.
Honestly,
I've devoted my life to the Cheng family all these years.
Ever since your dad passed away,
I've felt like a useless person.
But Gufeng Group is your dad's life's work.
He left it to you and your brother.
I can't just stand by
and watch others take it away.
I will definitely protect it for you.
But,
right now, I need your help.
Auntie,
don't worry.
I'll do my best.
Good.
Grandma.
Swimming helps you relax.
You know me best.
With so much happening at home recently,
I've been feeling really upset.
Only you
are considerate enough
to think of bringing Grandma out for fun.
Mrs. Cheng.
Ms. Sang.
Isn't that Coach Shen, who taught you frisbee?
Yes, it is.
Why is he here?
Mrs. Cheng.
Ms. Sang.
Long time no see.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
Coach Shen, are you...
I'm also a part-time swim coach.
What a coincidence.
Since Coach Shen is here,
why not let him take you swimming?
You can go take a rest then.
Then shall we...
Let's practice.
Careful.
Lin Wanmei has successfully blended Kista's wine.
Excellent.
Lin Wanmei.
Let's see how you talk your way out of this.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Careful.
Easy, easy.
Here, let me help you.
Good. Good. Very good.
What a beautiful day.
The fruity aroma and the scent of oak
instantly spread across the palate.
The texture of the tannin is also perfect.
And the finish is long.
This wine
has perfectly replicated Kista red wine's
essence and soul.
The lab in California
analyzed the wine's chemical composition,
and then made adjustments
to chemically replicate the original.
I want everyone to know
that whatever Kista can do,
I can do too.
Wanmei,
this wine
is indeed very good.
But you must know,
replicating red wine
has a huge impact on one's reputation.
Once the public finds out,
won't your reputation be ruined?
I'm also developing new products myself.
My new products
can help you too.
Can your wine
surpass Kista's?
Can it help me defeat her in a short time?
I won't admit defeat.
I've suffered for years at Gufeng Group.
I must prove myself.
I want everyone to know
that I, Lin Wanmei,
am not to be messed with.
This family is like a den of wolves.
Everyone is playing their own hidden game.
Calculating every move,
with undercurrents surging.
I only feel at peace when I'm here with you.
Dongdong,
I thought about it,
and you still have to leave.
I asked experts abroad.
They said there's still a chance you can stand again.
Sang Luo,
why are you so good to me?
Because you're not just family to me,
you're also my friend.
Yeah.
I want you to live well,
have a healthy body,
and be able to pursue the life you want.
Sang Luo,
I'm grateful for everything you've done.
But right now,
I don't want to leave yet.
Because here,
there's still someone I want to protect.
I don't want
to leave when she needs me.
Sang Luo,
once I've decided when to leave,
I will definitely
tell you right away.
Okay.
Then keep yourself safe.
You hear me?
I've noticed
that only when you're with Dongdong
do you act like a Cheng family member,
without having your thorns out.
Were you eavesdropping on us,
Little Uncle?
The thorns of a rose
never prick those who admire it.
They only pierce
the ones who try to control
and pluck it.
Sometimes I wonder,
as your Little Uncle,
I haven't been too bad to you, right?
But why do you always
target me at every turn?
When you, Little Uncle, can tolerate me
just as you tolerate yourself,
maybe then I'll treat you better.
So after all that,
it's somehow my fault.
I came here
just to tell you
that next week, Lin Wanmei
has decided to host a
Gufeng Group's new product Wine Tasting.
This is very important to Gufeng Group.
It should go smoothly, right?
Of course.
Rest assured, Little Uncle.
I promise
there will be a surprise beyond your expectations.
I'll look forward to it then.
I wonder what the new product is this time.
Everyone.
Welcome to our
intimate Wine Tasting.
Today...
Today, I'm highly honored to present this
new red wine,
Enchanted Dream.
This wine
blends the essence of various grapes,
and in its winemaking techniques,
it also features bold innovations.
I hope
it will bring you all
a unique tasting experience.
Cheers!
The aftertaste is indeed different.
Ms. Lin,
I just tasted your
Enchanted Dream red wine,
and found
its taste to be very unique.
Has this red wine
been improperly adulterated?
That's a baseless accusation.
The winemaking process of this wine
strictly follows regulations.
No improper adulteration is involved.
If that's the case,
why don't you show us
this red wine's
R&D records
and winemaking process,
so we can
verify them?
Yeah!
These
take time to prepare.
Hello, everyone.
Let me say a few words.
I am Cheng An.
Gufeng Group has always valued integrity.
Regarding this accusation,
we will conduct a thorough investigation.
Please rest assured.
Thank you all.
Yes, it must be thoroughly investigated!
Mr. Cheng is still trustworthy.
What are you doing!
Hello, everyone.
I am Sang Luo,
and also a daughter of the Cheng family.
Regarding today's red wine,
I can tell you all very clearly
that it is indeed adulterated.
Adulterated?
It really is adulterated!
She was so confident it wasn't just now.
But this isn't Ms. Lin Wanmei's fault.
This is a special segment
of today's Wine Tasting,
to show how adulterated wine differs
from traditionally made wine.
Taking this opportunity today,
I would also like to announce
my other identity to everyone.
Actually,
I am Kista.
She is Kista?
How is that possible?
I can't believe she's Kista!
I have accepted Gufeng Group's invitation,
and will soon take the position of
Director of Gufeng Group's R&D Department.
I believe that,
led by Ms. Lin Wanmei and myself,
Gufeng Group
will surely achieve new success.
Auntie Lin,
why don't you come up and say a few words?
Sang Luo,
you set me up!
Auntie Lin,
what did you say?
Speak up!
They can't hear you.
That's right.
It was a misunderstanding.
I also warmly welcome Kista,
who is Sang Luo,
to join our R&D Department.
I believe under our joint leadership,
we will definitely make
greater contributions to Gufeng Group.
Thank you.
Definitely!
They definitely can.
They certainly can.
Something to look forward to.
What a brilliant setup.
Why haven't you left yet, Little Uncle?
You don't have to wait for me here.
My ride will be here soon.
Cancel it.
I'll drive you.
It seems
Yi Kai has helped you a lot.
I was the one who asked Yi Kai
not to reveal my identity to anyone.
Stop being so passive-aggressive, Little Uncle.
Me, passive-aggressive?
In your eyes,
can't the Cheng family even compare to an outsider?
That's right.
Sometimes, the ones who push you into the abyss
are often the people closest to you.
From the moment you entered the Cheng family,
I knew there was more to you.
First, you used your title as Cheng Feng's
daughter to get into Gufeng Group.
Then, you used your identity as Kista
to secure your position.
You're quite impressive, young lady.
I entered the Cheng family
because I am a daughter of the Cheng family.
I entered Gufeng Group
based on my winemaking skills.
This was rightfully mine to begin with.
I hope you're telling the truth.
Let's go home.
Mom.
Thanks to Luo Luo today,
we managed to save the day.
Exactly.
Come.
Fortune favors the good.
Grandma.
Second Uncle.
If it isn't Master Kista.
How can we let Master Kista carry her own bag?
Come, come.
Let Second Uncle hold it for you.
Luo Luo.
The genius master winemaker, Kista.
You see,
you truly are a Cheng.
You inherited your father's great genes.
Which ultimately came from Grandma.
That's true.
You're not wrong.
Grandma,
I'm sorry.
I kept it a secret for so long.
You kept such wonderful news from Grandma?
If you had told Grandma earlier,
there'd be no room for those
unpresentable things
to prance around here.
Second Uncle has been thinking.
As for your position as director
of the R&D center,
just hold onto it for now.
Once Second Uncle pulls a few strings,
the CEO position
will be yours sooner or later.
Second Uncle,
don't make fun of me.
When it comes to seniority,
Auntie Lin is the most senior.
The position of the new CEO
absolutely belongs to Auntie Lin.
Only the incompetent rely on seniority.
Relying on underhanded tactics
to win people over...
It's an absolute joke.
Eldest daughter-in-law,
starting today, you will stay at home.
Don't go anywhere.
Take good care of the baby.
If anything happens to him,
you might just
get kicked out of the Cheng family.
Okay.
I'll follow your arrangements, Mom.
Auntie Lin,
you're here.
Grandma keeps talking about you.
She says you should rest at home
and focus on your recovery.
After all,
we won't rely on you for company matters.
It'll all be up to me.
For something like a work handover,
I still had to come in person.
Let me warn you, though.
Just how treacherous the R&D Department is,
you haven't truly witnessed yet.
Don't think that having some skills
means you can secure a foothold here.
The inner workings of this place
aren't something a naive girl like you
can easily figure out.
I know
there will definitely be challenges ahead.
But I'm capable of leading the R&D Department.
As for you,
since you're staying home, stop meddling
in company affairs.
Just enjoy your life.
Fine.
I'll wait and see.
I'd like to see
what kind of results you can achieve.
Don't let reality beat you
to a pulp,
begging me to come clean up your mess.
Well, if it isn't the new director.
Why are you
acting so high and mighty on day one?
Not even a hello to everyone?
R&D Department.
Where are all the red wine data sheets?
I need to get up to speed
on the current project's progress.
On the workstation.
Just ignore her, everyone.
Get back to work.
Mr. Cheng.
It's Sang Luo.
I'm currently in the R&D Department.
I want to confirm something with you.
Does the power to hire and fire in the
R&D Department lie with me?
That's right.
All matters in the R&D Department,
including staff hiring and management,
are entirely your responsibility.
You are the R&D Department Director.
Human Resources will cooperate with you.
You all heard that.
If anyone doesn't want to work under me,
you can get the hell out right now.
You just have Cheng An backing you up.
Like a fox hiding behind a tiger.
You think with him around,
you can do whatever you want?
Too bad this tiger listens to me.
If you don't like it, try me.
Let's see if you can last even one more day here.
What is this?
All these results
are just knockoffs of other people's wines.
There's zero breakthrough or innovation.
If this is the case,
what's the point of this department?
Zhao Yue,
what did you even brew?
It's practically slop.
You can't even get a simple thing right.
Manager Xiao...
I...
You're completely useless.
You're just wasting company resources here.
Manager Xiao...
I...
I'm really trying.
What is this garbage you brewed?!
The wine you make
is just as trashy as you are.
Does Gufeng Group let just anyone in?
People like you
should disappear from this company.
Get out of my sight.
Get out!
I'm sick of looking at you.
Indeed.
The texture of this wine is too rough.
You hear that?
Even the director says so.
What's your excuse now?
Xiaoxiao.
Where is your wine?
Let me try it.
This is really good.
Tell me.
This wine...
What kind of grapes is it made from?
Of course, it's our winery's
best Cabernet Sauvignon this year.
Along with my unique winemaking technique,
it creates this
one-of-a-kind fine wine.
Then tell me,
what is the tannin content of this wine?
Besides the grapes themselves,
this...
what other flavors does it have?
It's green tea.
When I was making this wine,
I tried adding some green tea.
I wanted to make the taste of the wine
a bit more complex.
Zhao Yue, right?
Your idea is very good.
And very innovative.
It just so happens
I'm planning to form an Innovation Team.
You can join too.
She's just useless.
I'm warning you,
stop bullying your colleagues.
And don't claim others' wine as your own.
From today on,
you'd better behave yourself,
otherwise I'll make sure you won't survive
a single day in the R&D Department.
Master.
It's me,
Xiaoxiao.
What's the situation?
Master,
you predicted this perfectly.
That Sang Luo,
she started winning people over right away.
She wants to establish some sort of
Innovation Team.
And she even recruited Zhao Yue.
The way I see it,
she just wants to poach the team you built
in the R&D Center
to establish her own authority.
I knew she wouldn't stay in her lane.
Once we take Sang Luo down,
the director position will be yours.
Got it, Master.
I definitely won't let you down.
Sang Luo,
you want to trample me underfoot?
I have plenty of ways to ruin your reputation.
When that time comes,
the R&D Department will still be my domain.
"Master," my foot.
You're just a washed-up has-been.
If it weren't for the director position,
who would want to take orders from you?
What's that smell?
It's so pungent.
It's sandalwood.
Mom, isn't this your favorite scent?
I grabbed the wrong one.
I'll change it for you right away.